{
    "id": "7177b365f1794aa4ad8baec3211bc6c6",
    "title": "So, to and for exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "53757799ea524e73b6c95c0f89d60f31",
            "title": "So, To And For",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Susie talked to the shy girl ………………………. she wouldn’t feel left out.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "for",
                        "to",
                        "so that"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I am going …………………… ask her out.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to",
                        "for",
                        "so"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "They aren’t going ……………………… come.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to",
                        "for",
                        "so"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Let’s have a break ………………… lunch.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to",
                        "so that",
                        "for"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The weather is stormy and will remain …………………. over the weekend.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "for",
                        "so",
                        "to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I offer you new lamps ………………… old.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to",
                        "for",
                        "so that"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "We could not see ……………………… smoke.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "because",
                        "for",
                        "since"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She went ………………………. the market.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "for",
                        "to",
                        "so"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She prefers dogs ………………….. cats.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "for",
                        "to",
                        "so"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "They got …………………… their destination.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to",
                        "for",
                        "so"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}